Decisions
I relinquish all ownership of this notebook.
このノートの所有権を…放棄する
I'm counting on you... take care of Misa.
頼んだぞ、海砂の事…
Stalker-san?
ストーカーさん…
Hey, Stalker-san? Where are you?
ねぇ、ストーカーさん
どこにいるの
Why don't you stop playing games now?
もうやめようよこんな遊び
…はぁ？
Stalker? What's she talking about?
ストーカー…どういうことだ
She's suddenly undergone a complete change in attitude...
急に態度が一変した
Just as I thought, as long as I have Ryuk's Death Note, even if I discard Rem's Death Note, I won't forget about Rem.
やはり…リュークのデスノートを持っていれば、
レムのノートを捨てても、
僕の記憶からレムが消えるわけでもない
But still, Rem... it's thanks to you bringing another Death Note into the human world that I've ended up in this...
それにしてもレム、
オマエが人間界にもう一冊ノート持ち込んだおかげで、
But still, Rem... it's thanks to you bringing another Death Note into the human world that I've ended up in this...
僕はこんな目に…
You really sure about this, Light?
本当にいいのか？ライト
Yeah.
ああ
You know, I never guessed the notebook I gave you would end up discarded in the ground somewhere.
まさか、
オレの渡したノートの最後は、土の中に捨てられるとはな
You know, I never guessed the notebook I gave you would end up discarded in the ground somewhere.
Listen Ryuk... for the moment, I've only hidden it in the ground.
いいかリューク、まだ土の中に隠してあるのであって
I will discard it... the very next time the word "discard" escapes my mouth.
捨てるのは…次に僕が「捨てる」という言葉を口にした時だ
Regardless of the context in which I say it, when I say that word, I'll mean it in relation to discarding the notebook.
その時は文脈に拘らず、その言葉を
「ノートを捨てる」という意味で口にする
Got it.
わかった
Stalker-san? This is a felony, you know, please stop...
ストーカーさん、これ犯罪だから、やめなさい
Stalker-san? Hey?
ストーカーさん、ね
She's been like this ever since she passed out...
一度気を失って、気付いてからずっとパターンだ…
Jeez, she really thinks she can feign innocence, doesn't she?
まったく、こんなのでとぼけられると思ってるんですかね
Ah, I know!
じゃあわかった
For now, why don't you just take off my blindfold?
とりあえず、目隠しだけでも取って
Stalker-san, I really want to see your face.
ストーカーさんの顔みたいな
Matsuda-san, call Mogi-san.
松田さん、模木さんに電話
えっ、ああ…
Here.
はい
Mogi-san, when you arrested Amane Misa, you said it was on suspicion of being the second Kira, didn't you?
模木さん、弥海砂を確保する時、
「第二のキラ容疑で」と言いましたよね？
Yes, exactly as you said.
はい、言われたとおり
We covered up her eyes and mouth from behind, and said clearly, so she could hear, "we're arresting you on suspicion of being the second Kira".
後ろから目と口を押さえ、「第二のキラ容疑で連行をする」と…
彼女には聞こえるように
She didn't attempt to resist the handcuffs or the blindfold. She seemed pretty resigned.
手錠、アイマスクなどをしても抵抗する様子はなく、
観念した様子でした
I'll give you my autograph and shake your hand.
サインもしてあげるし、握手も…
Oh, I know! I'll kiss you on the cheek!
あっそうだ、ほっぺにチューしてあげるから
Hey, Misa won't run away!
ね、海砂逃げないから…
We've been discussing the second Kira for a while already... why has she started talking about a stalker now?
あれだけ第二のキラとして話を進めてきたのに
何故今更ストーカーなどと…
Amane Misa.
弥海砂
Stalker-san, what do you want?
…ストーカーさん、なに？
Have you finally decided to release me?
帰す気になった？
Before you fell asleep, you were denying everything, and even went as far as saying "kill me", yet, now we have a senseless struggle like this?
寝る前まで殆ど黙秘し、「殺せ」とまで言っておきながら、
今更悪あがきか？
ん？何言ってるの？
What are you talking about?
Stalker-san, you were the one who knocked out and brought Misa here.
海砂を眠らせて連れてきたのストーカーさんでしょ？
What? You want to do an "Investigation of Amane Misa" or something?
なに？
「弥海砂、取り調べしちゃうぞ」とか、そういうのがしたいの？
Do you know why you're tied up like that?
君は今何故そこに縛られている
Why? It's because Misa's an idol, right?
何故って…海砂がアイドルだから？
But you know, Stalker-san, you're the first to have gone this far for me...
でもここまでしてくれたストーカーさんは、あなたが初めてだよ
Damn it, Amane!
こら！弥！
Stop messing around!
ふざけるのもいい加減にしろ！
I-I'm scared... what's going on?!
ひっ、怖い…
なんなの？もうこんなの嫌だ
I don't want this!
Let me go! Let me go!
放して、放してよ
Umm... that's right. I have to go to the bathroom again.
そうだ、またトイレ…
Bathroom! I want to go!
トイレ行きたい
You went to the bathroom only four minutes ago.
さっきトイレに行ってから四分しか経っていません
我慢してください
Please try to hold it.
What?! If I didn't say, I'd have to go here!
なによ！そう言わなきゃずっとこのままじゃない
また海砂のオシッコしてるところ見られるよ
You'll get to see Misa wet herself again, won't that be fun?!
楽しくない？この変態！
You pervert!
I'm... a pervert?
私が…変態…
Amane, let's be serious and continue our discussion from before you fell asleep.
弥、眠ってしまう前の話の続きを真面目にしよう
Do you know Yagami Light?
夜神月を知っているか？何故彼に近づいた？
How did you get to know him?
Why wouldn't I know my own boyfriend?!
自分の彼氏知らない訳ないでしょ
Before, she didn't confess a thing, yet now she's openly calling him her boyfriend?
あれだけ黙秘していたのに…
今度はあっさり彼氏か
Before, she didn't confess a thing, yet now she's openly calling him her boyfriend?
What's going on?
どうなってるんだ？
It's Light-kun.
月君からです
Turn off the video and audio.
影像、音声オフに
Understood.
はい
Yes?
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
I'm in room 2801 at the K.
K is the abbreviated name of the hotel.
ここはKの2801号室です
My son is coming here?
息子が…ここへ来るのか？
Ryuuzaki, it's as I said on the phone...
竜崎…電話でも言ったが、
I... might be Kira.
僕が…キラかもしれない…
D-Don't be stupid! What are you saying?! Light?!
馬…馬鹿な
何を言ってるんだ、月！
D-Don't be stupid! What are you saying?! Light?!
What's happened?! Huh?!
どうしたというんだ、はあ!!
I have no proof that Yagami Light is Kira.
夜神月がキラだという証拠もない…
Yet, you're saying "I might be Kira"... it's an act.
が、ここで「僕がキラかもしれない…」
演技だ
お前はキラかもでもなくキラだ
It's not that you "might be" Kira, you are Kira.
What on earth are you trying to do?
一体何をしようとしている
Father, if Ryuuzaki is L, it's not an exaggeration to say that he's the best detective in the world.
父さん、竜崎が L なら、世界一と言っても過言ではない探偵だ
That same L is labeling me as Kira. I have to be Kira.
その L が僕をキラだと決め付けている
きっと僕がキラなんだ…
W-What are you saying?! Light?!
な…なにを言ってるんだ、月…
The person who the FBI investigator Ray Penber was investigating from the time he came to Japan until he died...
FBI 捜査官、
レイ．ペンバーが日本に来てから死ぬまでに調べていた者…
The person who was in Aoyama on the 22nd of May...
5月22日に青山に行った者…
The person who Amane Misa, the suspected second Kira, immediately made advances on after coming here from Kanto...
そして…第二のキラ容疑の海砂が関東に出てきて、
真っ先に口説いた人間…
they're all me.
全て僕だ…
If I were in L's shoes, I'd deduce that I was Kira.
僕が L の立場でも、僕をキラだと推理する
This means that subconsciously, I might have become Kira.
これは…僕に自覚がないだけで…
僕が、キラなのかもしれないって事だ…
Light...
月…
I see... subconsciously, huh?
なるほど…
自覚がない…か
I don't even understand myself anymore.
もう…自分でも自分がわからなくなる…
Even though I'm not conscious of it, I could be killing people while I sleep or something!
僕に自覚がなくても、例えば寝ている間に、
もう一人の僕が殺人を犯しているのかもしれない
Even though I'm not conscious of it, I could be killing people while I sleep or something!
That you haven't.
それはありませんでした
っ？どういう意味だ竜崎
What do you mean, Ryuuzaki?!
To be honest, there was a period of five days where we set up surveillance cameras in your room.
実は月君の部屋に
五日間ほど監視カメラを付けていた時があったんです
Cameras?
カメラ…
Yes.
はい
You slept normally at night.
月君は夜、普通に寝ていました
月君が情報を得ていない時に
報道された犯罪者が死んでいった事から、
Having seen that criminals continued to die, despite you having no access to information about them,
I concluded not that you were innocent; merely that, if you were Kira, you would not give yourself away on camera.
「キラではない」ではなく、
カメラが付けていても、
「キラとしてのボロは出さない」と判断しました
"If you were Kira, you wouldn't give yourself away", huh?
「キラとしてのボロは出さない」、か…
That could be true.
実際そうなるかもしれない
If I'm honest, I've sometimes thought that some criminals would be better off dead.
正直に言うが、
僕はある程度の重犯罪者は、死んだ方がいいとも思っている
If I'm honest, I've sometimes thought that some criminals would be better off dead.
I think anyone who thinks this way could become Kira.
こういう考えを持っている人間なら、
誰でもキラになり得ると思うんだ
Light-kun! I'm exactly the same.
月君、それは僕だって同じだ
I often find myself thinking that certain people would be better off dead, but that doesn't mean we would really go and kill them, right?
こんな奴死んだ方がいいと思う事なんて、しょっちゅうある
でも、だからって本当に人を殺したりしない
そうだろ？
Besides, criminals that you had no knowledge of continued to die.
それに、月君が情報を得てない、犯罪者が死んでいったんだ
それは、監視カメラが証明してくれた
The surveillance cameras proved this!
N-No... at the time, we didn't have enough manpower, and only watched his movements inside of the house.
い…いや
あの時は捜査員不足もあり、在宅時しか見ていない
It's not like we watched him 24/7 over those five days, so he may have had a way of killing people when he was out of the house.
五日間、24時間監視していたわけじゃない
家にいない時に殺人をする方法があったのかもしれない
Did you predict that things would turn out this way, Yagami Light?
こうなる事を予想していたのか夜神月…
But, if we detain him like Amane, and criminals continue to die... that would make Yagami Light not Kira, right?
しかし…弥のようにこれから長期渡り拘束したとして、
今後世に出る犯罪者が死んでいたら…
But, if we detain him like Amane, and criminals continue to die... that would make Yagami Light not Kira, right?
夜神月はキラではない、か…
Is that your plan?
それを狙っているのか…
Somehow I don't like the way this conversation is heading, but...
何か、私には少し話しの展開が気に入りませんが…
Fine.
いいでしょう
We'll restrain Yagami Light, and imprison him long term.
夜神月の手足を縛り、長期間牢に監禁
な、なにを…
W-What?!
Light-kun... imprisoned?
月君を…か…監禁!?
If we're going to do this, we'll start now, by making sure he never goes anywhere I can't see him.
その代わり、やるなら今からです
一度も私の目の届かぬ場所に行くこともなく
T-This is stupid! There's no way my son could be Kira!
馬…馬鹿な
息子がキラであるはずが…
My son would never--!
大体、そんなこと息子が…
It's okay, father.
いや、父さん
Light?!
月…
I can't continue chasing Kira, when deep down, I don't even know whether I'm Kira or not.
僕も…このまま自分がキラではないのかと、
心のどこかで悩みながら…キラを追っていく事はできない
In return, until you have absolutely no doubt about whether I'm innocent or Kira, no matter what happens or what I say, don't let me out.
その代わり、竜崎が
僕がキラだとわかるか、キラじゃないと納得するまで、
In return, until you have absolutely no doubt about whether I'm innocent or Kira, no matter what happens or what I say, don't let me out.
僕が何を言おうと、どんな状態になろうと…
絶対自由にしないでくれ
I understand.
わかりました
Yagami-san, can you come up with an excuse for Light-kun's absence for your family?
夜神さん
家族の方に月君がいなくなる理由、今から作れますか？
I mean... please do so.
いや、作ってください
A-All of a sudden, you can't expect me to--!
そ、そんなこと急に言われても…
In the first place, I can't understand why my son has to be imprisoned!
大体、何故息子が牢なんかに…
You're being stubborn, father.
しつこいよ父さん
ラ…
月…
This is the only method by which I'll be able to convince myself.
そうしないと、僕自身が納得できないんだ
Are you serious, Light?
本気なのか？月…
Yes.
ああ
By sealing away my freedom, I'm going to win against the fear that Kira lurks inside me!
僕は自分の自由を封じる事で、
自分の中に潜むキラの恐怖に勝つ！
Aizawa-san, I'm counting on you.
相沢さん、お願いします
Okay.
はい
Imprisonment: Day One
Now all that remains is to discard the notebook.
あとは…ノートを捨てるだけだ
I'm gonna be stuck with no apples to eat again?
また、リンゴ食えなくなるのか？
Ryuuzaki, I want you to remove me from the investigation.
竜崎…
私をこの捜査本部から外してくれ
Chief!
局長…
The one currently imprisoned under suspicion of being Kira is my own son.
今、キラとして疑われ監禁されているのは私の息子…
I have no right to be here.
私は、ここにいる資格はない
Even when we were discussing his imprisonment, I tried to prevent it due to my own personal feelings.
監禁するか否か、さっき話していた時も、
私は一人私情で息子を監禁させないとしていた
That's right.
そうでしたね、私情を挟むなんて駄目ですね
You shouldn't let your personal feelings get involved.
I-If it turns out that my son is Kira, I don't know what I'd do.
こ…これで…
もし、息子がキラだという事にでもなったら…
I-If it turns out that my son is Kira, I don't know what I'd do.
私は、どんな行動を取るか…
Yes... it's not unimaginable that you may think to kill your son and then yourself.
はい、夜神さんなら息子さんを殺し、自分も死ぬ…
などと考えなくもなさそうです
I agree, it's better that you aren't here.
私もここに夜神さんを置かないのは賛成です
Ryuuzaki, I'd like you to imprison me as well.
竜崎、私も監禁してくれないか
Right now, I'm calm.
想い
今は冷静だが、息子への感情でいつ何をするか…
But I have no idea what I might do, due to feelings for my son.
I thought that you might say something like this, so I've asked Watari to make the necessary arrangements.
そう言い出す可能性があると想い、
ワタリに準備はさせていますが…
I thought that you might say something like this, so I've asked Watari to make the necessary arrangements.
But, though you will be imprisoned,
ただし、夜神さんは監禁といっても、
今までどおり携帯の電源はたまに入れ、
家族や外部との交信を普通に行う
you will have your cell phone turned on, now and again as usual, and will continue to communicate with your family and the outside world.
Light-kun won't be informed of this, and if he talks to you, we need him to think that you're still part of this investigation.
月君にはその事実を教えず、
月君が話しかけてきたら、この本部にいる様に思わせ会話する
Light-kun won't be informed of this, and if he talks to you, we need him to think that you're still part of this investigation.
Even while you are imprisoned, you will be kept up to date with the investigation at all times.
そして夜神さんには、
監禁された中でも、全ての捜査状況を随時報告する
Even while you are imprisoned, you will be kept up to date with the investigation at all times.
Is that fine with you?
それでいいですか？
I owe you one, Ryuuzaki.
恩に着る、竜崎…
Imprisonment: Day Three
Stalker-san, I want to take a bath.
ストーカーさん、お風呂入りたい
I'm guessing you know where I live anyway... fetch me a change of clothes...
どうせ私のうち知ってるんでしょ、着替え持ってきてよ
Things are getting super crazy around here again...
またすごい事になってきたな…
I just feel really bad for the Chief.
僕はもう、局長が気の毒で…
Ryuuzaki, how is it going?
竜崎、どうだ？
Were there any reports of new criminals that were likely to be targeted by Kira yesterday or the day before?
昨日、一昨日に、キラに殺されてもおかしくない、
新たな犯罪者は報道されたか？
And if they were reported, have they been killed by Kira?
報道されたのなら、キラに殺されたか？
There have been reports of some likely criminals, but ever since you were imprisoned, not a single criminal has been killed.
それなりの犯罪者が何人が報道されましたが、
月君を監禁してから、誰一人犯罪者は殺されなくなりました
They've stopped being killed?
殺されなくなった…
Really?
本当か？
はい
Yes.
そうか…
I see... looks like they're finally going to decide that I'm Kira.
いよいよ僕がキラって事になりそうだな…
I really want to eat an apple...
リンゴ食いてぇな
What's going on?
どうなってるんだ…
I thought that even if I imprisoned Yagami Light, the killings would continue.
夜神月を監禁しても、
キラの犯罪者への裁きは止まらないと読んでいたが、
Yet, they've completely stopped.
実際はぴったりと止まった…
It looked as though he was voluntarily offering to imprison himself, but the way this is going, he'll end up as Kira.
夜神月は自分から監禁を望んだように見えたが…
これでは、「夜神月はキラ」だったという事になる
It looked as though he was voluntarily offering to imprison himself, but the way this is going, he'll end up as Kira.
Now the question remains, whether or not he was conscious of being Kira.
こうなると問題は、キラの自覚があったかなかったか…
Even if he is Kira, does he think that pretending to be unaware of it will make it alright?
自分がキラであったとしても、
「自覚がなかった」と押し通しさえすれば済むと考えているのか
Even if he is Kira, does he think that pretending to be unaware of it will make it alright?
This isn't like Yagami Light... no, it isn't like Kira.
夜神月らしくない…
いや、キラらしくない…
This isn't like Yagami Light... no, it isn't like Kira.
Imprisonment: Day Five
It's no good, Light.
ダメだライト…
If I don't eat an apple soon--!
そろそろリンゴ食わないと…
In any case, the only thing to do is to be patient... even if there's nothing to do.
とにかく、我慢するしかないな…
暇でも…
Stalker-san... you won't be able to sell a video of me just sitting down.
ストーカーさん…ずっと座ってるだけのビデオじゃ売れないよ
Yagami-san seems to be in a much worse condition than Light-kun or Amane.
月君や弥より、夜神さんの方が危ないですね
Well, of course!
そりゃそうですよ
月君を拘束してから五日、
During the five days Light-kun has been imprisoned, not a single reported criminal has died.
その間、新たに報道された犯罪者は一人も死なない
In this kind of situation, it's harder on the parent than the suspect.
こういう時は、本人より親の方が辛いんじゃないかな…
As a result, this has pretty much decided that Light-kun is Kira.
これでも、殆ど月君がキラだったって事は決まりだからな…
Yagami-san...
夜神さん
What is it?!
どうした？
Is it good or bad news?!
いい知らせか!?悪い知らせか!?
...umm, no. I think it would be better if you don't think too much about this.
あっいえ…あまり思いつめない様にと…
No matter what you're thinking as you sit there, it won't affect the end results.
夜神さんがそこで深刻に考えて込んでいても、結果は同じです
Why don't you rest in a more relaxing environment?
どうでしょう？
そんな所ではなく、もっと気の休まるところで休養しては…
Don't be ridiculous!
馬鹿な！
こんな状況で気の休まる所などない！
There is no such thing as a relaxing environment in my current circumstances!
今の私には、ここが一番落ち着く
This is the most relaxing place for me now.
No matter what the result is, when I leave here, it will be with my son!
どんな結果になろうと、
ここから出る時は息子と一緒だ！
I understand.
わかりました…
Imprisonment: Day Seven
Light-kun, it's only been a week, but you look exhausted.
月君
まだ一週間ですがさすがにやつれてきてます
Are you okay?
大丈夫ですか？
It's probably about time... now that I've gotten this far...
そろそろいいだろう
ここまで来れば…
Yeah.
ああ…自分でも格好のいい状態とはとても思えないが…
Even I can't say that I look too good at the moment... but such meaningless pride... I'll discard it!
そんなくだらないプライドは…
捨てる！
ん？
Alright.
Gotcha!
はいよ
See ya.
じゃあな
Huh? Why am I doing this?
何で僕は、こんな事をしているんだ…
Ryuuzaki!
竜崎、
I know I chose to be imprisoned and go through with this, but I've just realized, there's no point in this!
確かに僕は監禁される事を承諾し、こうすることを選んだ…
しかし今はっきりと気付いた
I know I chose to be imprisoned and go through with this, but I've just realized, there's no point in this!
こんな事をしていても無駄だ
Because I am not Kira.
何故なら、僕はキラじゃない！
Hurry up and let me out of here!
早くここから出してくれ！
駄目です
I can't do that.
Until I'm sure whether you're Kira or not, no matter what you say, I won't release you. That was the promise.
キラかキラでないか判断できるまで、
月君が何を言おうと出さない約束です
There was something wrong with me that time!
あの時、僕はどうかしていたんだ！
Do you actually believe that it's possible to do what Kira does and not be aware of it?!
キラという殺人鬼がやってきた事、
自覚無しでやっていたなんて思えるか!?
I am not conscious of being Kira, therefore I am not Kira!
キラとしての自覚がない僕は、キラじゃない！
I also believe that Kira cannot be unaware of who they are, but if you are Kira, then it all adds up.
私も、
キラが自分をキラだと自覚してないなどとは考えていません
I also believe that Kira cannot be unaware of who they are, but if you are Kira, then it all adds up.
しかし月君がキラだとしたら全ての辻褄は合います
As soon as we imprisoned you, the killings stopped.
月君を監禁したとたん、キラによる殺人が止まったのですから
Listen carefully, Ryuuzaki, there's no way I'm lying.
いいか竜崎、よく聞いてくれ
僕は絶対に嘘など言っていない…
僕はキラじゃない！
I'm not Kira!
I can only imagine that I've been set up!
こうしている事も…はめられたとしか思えない！
What's going on, Yagami Light?
どうしたんだ夜神月…
What you're saying is all over the place... but why do I sense I'm getting close to the root of the problem?
言っている事がめちゃくちゃだ…
しかし、なぜか真に迫る感じだ…
Hurry up and let me out!
早く出してくれ、時間の無駄だ！
This is a waste of time!
No. I can't let you out.
駄目です、出すことはできません
Damn it! How did it turn out like this...
くそっ…
何でこんなことに…
Damn it! How did it turn out like this...
What's going on? This isn't like Light-kun.
どうなってるんだ？月君らしくないな
He's contradicting himself and isn't being logical at all.
前言を撤回しているし、全然論理的でもない
Now that the murdering of criminals has stopped, there's no way we can release him.
犯罪者が殺されなくなった以上、監禁を解くわけにはいかない…
Even I have realized that much.
そのくらい、僕だってわかりますよ
Well, no matter what anyone says, at this rate, Yagami Light will be confirmed as Kira. We can close the case, and everyone will be happy.
まぁ、誰が何を言おうと、
このままなら、
夜神月がキラで事件解決って事でいいんじゃないか？
Well, no matter what anyone says, at this rate, Yagami Light will be confirmed as Kira. We can close the case, and everyone will be happy.
Imprisonment: Day Fifteen
What's going on?!
どうなってるんですか？
Two weeks' worth of criminals were taken out in one shot yesterday!
昨日一日で、二週間以上裁かれていなかった犯罪者が一気に…
Yeah... Kira is back.
Kira Returns
キラ復活だ
Have you told the Chief?
局長には伝えたんですか？
No, not yet.
いや、まだ…
Chief! Kira is on the move!
局長、キラが動き出しました
What?!
何っ？
Kira was just resting.
キラは休んでいただけです
また犯罪者への裁きが始まりました！
The judgment of criminals has begun again!
ほ…本当か松田っ？
I-Is this true, Matsuda?!
じ、じゃあ息子は…
S-So my son... I can't say I'm happy that the killings have started again, but this means that the suspicions surrounding my son...
殺人が起きて喜んではならぬが、これで息子の疑いは…
いや…竜崎の事だ…白とは言うまい…
no, I know Ryuuzaki won't say he's completely "white"...
Let's go with "grey" then.
では…灰色で
Hear that Chief?!
聞こえましたか局長
Yeah.
ああ、ほとんど黒だったんだ…よかった…
So, he was mainly "black" before...
Thank goodness.
I'm sure that it's a "grey" that's nearly indistinguishable from "white".
多分、限りなく白に近いグレーですよ
Next, we should tell Light-kun--
じゃあ、月君には…
Matsuda!!
松田！
いや、松田さん止めてください
I mean, Matsuda-san, please stop.
"Matsuda"?
松田…
Please don't tell Light-kun.
月君には教えないで下さい
ど、どうして…
W-Why?
Light-kun...
月君
What is it, Ryuuzaki?
なんだ…竜崎…
No criminals have been judged for over the past two weeks now.
もう二週間以上、新たな犯罪者が裁かれていません
いい加減キラである事を自白してもらえませんか
Why don't you just admit that you are Kira?
You're being stupid, Ryuuzaki.
馬鹿を言うな竜崎
You're wrong.
おまえは間違っている…
I'm not surprised that you think I'm Kira from the way the investigation has been going, but this is a trap!
今までの捜査状況から、
僕をキラだと推理するのはわかるが、これは罠だ！
I'm not Kira!
僕はキラじゃない！
Use the zoom or whatever to look closely at my eyes!
ズームにでもなんでもして、僕の目を見てくれ！
Are these the eyes of someone who's lying?!
これが…嘘をついてる人間の目か？
Amane, are you sure you don't know who Kira is?
弥、本当にキラが誰なのか知らないんだな
This, again?
はぁ？またそれ？海砂が知りたいよ
Misa would like to know that herself.
Kira is a superhero that killed the criminal who murdered Misa's parents.
キラは、
海砂の親を殺した強盗を裁いてくれた…正義の味方だもん
I have no idea what's going on...
何がなんだかわからない…
To be continued
馬…馬鹿な…
待ってくれ父さん！
ここで死んでも、真相は何もわからないままだ！
僕よりも L を信じるのか!?
父さんーー!!